Guide to the Stephen S. Fuller papers, 1932, 1956-2016
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center
Stephen S. Fuller papers
1932, 1956-2016
C0298
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center.
18 linear ft.
This collection includes economic reports, manuscripts, maps, newspaper clippings, and photographs. This collection contains materials from 1932 and 1956-2016
Fuller, Stephen S., 9999-9999
Box 1-45
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Collection donated by Stephen S. Fuller in October 2016 and December 2016
Biographical Information
Dr. Stephen S. Fuller received a Bachelor's degree in Economics from Rutgers University and a Doctorate in Regional Planning and Economic Development from Cornell University. He has authored hundreds of articles, papers, and reports about the Washington, D.C. area's economic development.
Dr. Fuller joined the George Mason University staff in 1994, serving as Professor of Public Policy. He also served as the Director of the Ph.D. Program of Public Policy from July 1998-2002. Fuller was chosen by the George Mason University Board of Visitors to be a University Professor in September 2001. He also served as a Dwight Schar Faculty Chair. Dr. Fuller is now the Director of The Stephen S. Fuller Institute.
Before joining the George Mason University faculty, Dr. Fuller served on the faculty at George Washington University as Chairman of the Department of Urban Planning and Real Estate Development, as well as spending one year as Director of Doctoral Programs for the School of Business and Public Management.
Scope and Content
This collection includes photographs, maps, and numerous reports with topics ranging from construction, transportation, federal spending, employment trends, population growth, and economic forecasts within Washington, D.C., Maryland, and Virginia. The collection is arranged into four series:
Series 1: Virginia (1959-2015) includes economic reports, maps, photographs, and planning documents.
Series 2: Maryland (1971-2011) includes economic reports and planning documents.
Series 3: Washington, D.C. (1932, 1956-2016) includes economic reports, federal spending reports, census data, magazines, maps, and planning documents.
Series 4: Reports from outside the Washington, D.C. region (1959-2012) includes economic reports, enviromental reports, testimonies, and planning documents.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged by region.
Series 1: Virginia, 1959-2015 (Boxes 1-12)
Series 2: Maryland, 1971-2011 (Boxes 12-14)
Series 3: Washington, D.C., 1932, 1956-2016 (Boxes 14-37)
Series 4: Reports from outside the Washington, D.C. region, 1959-2012 (Boxes 37-44)
Index Terms
Persons:
Fuller, Stephen S., 9999-9999
Subjects:
Economic--United States.; Northern Virginia.; Planning--Virginia, United States.; Real estate development--United States; Transportation--Virginia, Northern.; Transportation-- Washington Metropolitan Area--Planning.
Document Types:
Correspondence.; Maps.; Newspapers.; Photographs.
Contents List
- Series 1: Virginia, 1959-2015 (Boxes 1-12)
  This series includes economic reports, maps, photographs, and planning documents.
  - Reports on the economic impact of George Mason University on Washington, D.C. area economies, December 2005-July 2013 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Reports on the economic impact of George Washington University on Washington, D.C. area economies, September 1993-February 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Reports on the economic impact of Universities on Washington, D.C. area economies, April 1997-November 2008 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Economic and fiscal impact analysis for Prince William County, Virginia, April-July 1998 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Economic and fiscal impact analysis for Frederick County, Virginia, April-May 2000 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Reports on the economic impact of housing developments on Northern Virginia (1 of 4), June 2011-December 2012 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Reports on the economic impact of housing developments on Northern Virginia (2 of 4), January-September 2014 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Reports on the economic impact of housing developments on Northern Virginia (3 of 4), January 2015-April 2016 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Reports on the economic impact of housing developments on Northern Virginia (4 of 4), March-August 2016 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - "Understanding the Local Housing Market", February 2007 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Tourism brochures for Alexandria, Virginia, December 1989-1995 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 8.5x11 inch black and white photographs of Alexandria, Virginia, December 1990 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Maps and charts of Historic Alexandria, Virginia, 1959-1973 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Alexandria, Virginia waterfront design plan, May 1983 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Economic and fiscal impact reports for Alexandria, Virginia (1 of 3), 1980-1999 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Economic and fiscal impact reports for Alexandria, Virginia (2 of 3), September 2002-April 2007 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Economic and fiscal impact reports for Alexandria, Virginia (3 of 3), May 2007-February 2011 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - "Housing in Anne Arundel County", April 1978 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Economic and fiscal impact reports for Falls Church, Virginia, 1995-2002 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - "The Fiscal Implications of Local Economic Development Strategies", October 1990 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - "The Future of the Northern Virginia Economy" (1 of 3), May 16, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - "The Future of the Northern Virginia Economy" (2 of 3), May 28, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - "The Future of the Northern Virginia Economy" (3 of 3), May 12, 1998-May 26, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - George Mason University Economic Conference proceedings (1 of 3), 1994-1998 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - George Mason University Economic Conference proceedings (2 of 3), 1999-2002 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - George Mason University Economic Conference proceedings (3 of 3), 2003-2005 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - George Mason University conference speech notes, January 2001-2005 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Reports on the Fairfax County economy (1 of 5), 1996-1998 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Reports on the Fairfax County economy (2 of 5), 1999-2001 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Reports on the Fairfax County economy (3 of 5), 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Reports on the Fairfax County economy (4 of 5), 2004-2008 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Reports on the Fairfax County economy (5 of 5), 2009-2010 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Reports on the Loudon County economy (1 of 3), 2000 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Reports on the Loudon County economy (2 of 3), 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Reports on the Loudon County economy (3 of 3), 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Economic database content for Southern Virginia (1 of 2), 1991-1994 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Economic database content for Southern Virginia (2 of 2), 1991-1994 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - "The Fiscal Impact of Meadowbrook Farm of Jefferson County, Virginia", December 2000 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - "Measuring Fiscal Impact County Government", October 8, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - "A Fiscal Impact Analysis By Land Use Category: 2000:2030", August 2002 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Report on policy challenges for local jurisdictions, October 25, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Articles about Northern Virginia and Washington, D.C. economies, 1993-2004 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - "The Fiscal Impact of The Haven Part II at celebrate Virginia on the City of Fredericksburg", February 2011 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Virginia's school readiness report card, July 19, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Report on workforce development in the Commonwealth of Virginia, August 5, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - "The Impact of Metrorail on Loudon County's Economic Future", May 9, 2012 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - The Economic and Fiscal Impact of the Proposed Moss Neck Quarry on Caroline County, Virginia", February 2014 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - "The Fiscal Impact of the Proposed Midwood Age-Restricted Community on Prince William County, April 2014 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - "The Economic and Fiscal Impact of Alexander's Crossing on Spotsylvania County, Virginia", October 2014 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Report on the changing federal procurement patterns on Northern Virginia, July 2015 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Proposed 2016 Montgomery County budget, January 2015 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - "The Economic and Fiscal Impact of Commercial Use of the O'Toole Property on the Town of Purceville, Virginia", June 2015-2016 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Lyles-Crouch homecoming notes, circa 1990 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Report on Arlington real estate development, January 1994 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Northern Virginia 2030 Workforce Study, circa 2012 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Studies for population growth and commuting in Northern Virginia, circa 2010 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Torti Gallas and Partners presentation on Reston Station building plans, circa 2012 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Report on Northern Virginia in the global marketplace, September 25, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Report on the real estate market in Fairfax County, Virginia, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Dulles Greenway Program, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Fairfax County fold-out map, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Tysons Corner planning documents (1 of 3), 1990-2008 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Tysons Corner planning documents (2 of 3), 2008 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Tysons Corner planning documents (3 of 3), 2008-2009 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Reports on the Arlington County economy (1 of 2), December 1996 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Reports on the Arlington County economy (2 of 2), August 1999-April 2004 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Reports on job growth and residential development in Fairfax County (1 of 2), 1975-2005 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Reports on job growth and residential development in Fairfax County (2 of 2), June 1997-July 2009 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Reports on the Rosslyn-Ballston Corridor, May 1989 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - "Columbia Plaza" by Edward Noyes, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - "The Impact of Jiffy Lube Live on the Prince William County Economy", February 2012 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - "National Museum of Americans in Wartime: A Visitor Study", July 26, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - "The Impact of Sixteen Proposed Projects on the Commonwealth of Virginia", January 31, 2011 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Report on Crystal City Transportation, January 1986 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - "The Benefits of Privately Financing the Capital Beltway HOT Lanes Project", April 2009 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - "The Economic Impact of the Capital Beltway HOT Lanes in 2015", December 2009 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - "Economic and Fiscal Impacts of a Major League Baseball Franchise and Stadium on the Commonwealth of Virginia", July 2000 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Market analysis for a hotel and conference center in Quantico, Virginia, May 2011 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Fiscal Impact of Metrorail on The Commonwealth of Virginia, November 1985 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Metropolitan economic scorecard, July 1997 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Reports on workforce trends from 2010-2022 in Northern Virginia, 2011-2013 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - "Montgomery County's Future Workforce: Net New and Replacement Jobs and Educational Requirements", February 2012 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - "The Fiscal Impact of the Proposed Chancellorsville Development on Spotsylvania County, Virginia", September 2002 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - "Impact Fees and Student Generation Factors in Jefferson County, West Virginia", October 2003 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - "Economic Opportunities in the Fredericksburg Region", November 2003 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - "The Fiscal Impact of Vinton Farm on Jefferson County, West Virginia", December 2003 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - "The Economic and Fiscal Impact of the Proposed New Market Quarry on Prince William County", June 2004 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - "The Unstoppable Freight Train of Population Growth", February 23, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - "A Fiscal Impact Analysis by Land Use Category: 2003-2023", August 2004 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - "The Economic Impact of Parking Taxes", September 2005 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - "The Potential Impact of DOD Agency Relocation on the Northern Virginia and Statewide Economies", August 2004 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Reports on the impact of micron technology on Northern Virginia, September 2006 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - "The Economic and Fiscal Impact of the Proposed Rocky Run Village on Stafford County, Virginia", March 2005 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - "The Fiscal Impacts of Alternative Proposals for the Downtown Herndon Development Plan", Mach 2005 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - "The Fiscal Impact of Hazel Run on Spotsylvania County, Virginia", February 2005 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Report on commuter labor in the Fredericksburg region, October 2006 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - "The Economic and Fiscal Impact of the Town Center at Aquia Proposed Project on Stafford County, Virginia", October 2007 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Brandywine Crossing zoning map amendment application, February 2007 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Reports on the sales of heavy construction equipment, May 2008 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - "The Impact of Price Increases for Electricity on the Economy of the Commonwealth of Virginia", February 15, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Report on Stafford County's Proposed Land Use Plan, August 2008 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Reports on the Northern Virginia economy, 1994-2011 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Bulletin congressional internal publication, January 1998-October 2001 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Reports on Northern Virginia transportation, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Reports Northern Virginia's economy, September 2001-October 2011 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Northern Virginia economic indicators, September 19, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Publications about transportation issues in Northern Virginia, July 2002-January 2012 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Reports on the vulnerability of the Northern Virginia economy, 1993-1994 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Reports on the future of Northern Virginia's economy, March 1995-December 2009 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Series 2: Maryland, 1971-2011 (Boxes 12-14)
  This series includes economic reports and planning documents.
  - Reports on the Charles County economy, 1998-2001 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Targeted industry study for Charles County, Maryland, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Reports on the Prince George's County economy, May 2002-March 2012 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Program for Prince George's County Economic Summit, November 28, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Prince William County Economic Fiscal Impact Study, July 1999 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - "The Fiscal and Economic Impact of Annexing the Proposed Brunswick Crossing Development to the City of Brunswick, Maryland", October 18, 2011 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - "Economic and Fiscal Outlook: US, Maryland and Anne Arundel County", April 9, 2011 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Agricultural zoning report for Maryland and Delaware, April 20, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - "Fiscal Trends in Southern Maryland Past, Present and Future", November 1989 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - "The Economic Impact of the Beaver Creek Quarry on Washington County, Maryland", July 2005 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - "The Fiscal Impact of Housing in Frederick County, Maryland Fiscal Year 2005", September 2006 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - "Impact of the Proposed Development of Lot 31 on the Economy of Montgomery County", circa 2000 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - "The Impact of the Proposed Clemson Center Project on the Economy or the City of Frederick", February 2008 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Reports on the future of the Anne Arundel County area economy, 2011 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - "The Economic Impact of The Baltimore Zoo", November 1996 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Reports on Montgomery County economic trends 1950-1990, December 1991 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Maryland Services Sector strategy papers, July 13, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Reports on the Metropolitan Baltimore Economy, September 1972-June 1987 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Series 3: Washington, D.C., 1932, 1956-2016 (Boxes 14-37)
  This series includes economic reports, federal spending reports, census data, magazines, maps, and planning documents.
  - The Baltimore Washington Common Market, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - RIMS II multipliers for the Washington, D.C. area (1 of 3), 1997-2010 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - RIMS II multipliers for the Washington, D.C. area (2 of 3), 1997-2010 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - RIMS II multipliers for the Washington, D.C. area (3 of 3), 1997-2010 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Technology and the Washington, D.C. economy (1 of 2), 1985-1997 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Technology and the Washington, D.C. economy (2 of 2), 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Reports on the economic impact of spending within Washington, D.C.'s private sector (1 of 2), 1991-2006 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Reports on the economic impact of spending within Washington, D.C.'s private sector (2 of 2), 1991-2006 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - The Washington Post Magazine, April-August 2008 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Reports on the future of Washington, D.C.'s economy (1 of 4), June 1990-October 1994 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Reports on the future of Washington, D.C.'s economy (2 of 4), October 1994-June 2001 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Reports on the future of Washington, D.C.'s economy (3 of 4), circa 2005 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Reports on the future of Washington, D.C.'s economy (4 of 4), circa 2005 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Federal procurement in Washington, D.C. (1 of 9), 1999 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Federal procurement in Washington, D.C. (2 of 9), 2000 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Federal procurement in Washington, D.C. (3 of 9), 2001 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Federal procurement in Washington, D.C. (4 of 9), 2002 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Federal procurement in Washington, D.C. (5 of 9), 2002 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Federal procurement in Washington, D.C. (6 of 9), 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Federal procurement in Washington, D.C. (7 of 9), 2005 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Federal procurement in Washington, D.C. (8 of 9), 2006-2009 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Federal procurement in Washington, D.C. (9 of 9), 2010-2015 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Reports on the economic impact of museums on Washington, D.C. (1 of 4), 1979-2000 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Reports on the economic impact of museums on Washington, D.C. (2 of 4), June 2000 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Reports on the economic impact of museums on Washington, D.C. (3 of 4), November 2003-December 2005 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Reports on the economic impact of museums on Washington, D.C. (4 of 4), 2006 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Museum visitor forms and reports, circa 2000 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Reports on federal spending in the Washington, D.C. area (1 of 5), circa 1980 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Reports on federal spending in the Washington, D.C. area (2 of 5), June 1991-March 1994 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Reports on federal spending in the Washington, D.C. area (3 of 5), December 1995-May 1996 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Reports on federal spending in the Washington, D.C. area (4 of 5), September 1995-October 1996 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Reports on federal spending in the Washington, D.C. area (5 of 5), 1997 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Fold-out maps of the Washington, D.C. area, 1992-1996 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Reports on workforce trends in the Washington, D.C. area (1 of 7), June 1980-January 1985 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Reports on workforce trends in the Washington, D.C. area (2 of 7), December 1984-October 1985 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Reports on workforce trends in the Washington, D.C. area (3 of 7), January 1985-June 2005 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Reports on workforce trends in the Washington, D.C. area (4 of 7), 1987-1993 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Reports on workforce trends in the Washington, D.C. area (5 of 7), November 1994-June 1997 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Reports on workforce trends in the Washington, D.C. area (6 of 7), December 1997-February 1998 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Reports on workforce trends in the Washington, D.C. area (7 of 7), 2003-2013 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Reports on real estate development in the Washington, D.C. area (1 of 7), 1975-1982 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Reports on real estate development in the Washington, D.C. area (2 of 7), 1985-1989 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Reports on real estate development in the Washington, D.C. area (3 of 7), 1989-1993 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Reports on real estate development in the Washington, D.C. area (4 of 7), February 1998 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Reports on real estate development in the Washington, D.C. area (5 of 7), March 2000-2001 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Reports on real estate development in the Washington, D.C. area (6 of 7), 2003-2012 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Reports on real estate development in the Washington, D.C. area (7 of 7), 2012-2013 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Reports on federal construction projects in the Washington, D.C. area (1 of 6), 1972-2016 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Reports on federal construction projects in the Washington, D.C. area (2 of 6), 1972-2016 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Reports on federal construction projects in the Washington, D.C. area (3 of 6), 1972-2016 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Reports on federal construction projects in the Washington, D.C. area (4 of 6), 1972-2016 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Reports on federal construction projects in the Washington, D.C. area (5 of 6), 1972-2016 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Reports on federal construction projects in the Washington, D.C. area (6 of 6), 1972-2016 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - "The Environmental Industry: Growth Trends and Significance to the Washington Area Economy", September 19, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - "Restructuring A Single-Sector Centrally Planned Economy: Lessons From Daqing, China", circa 2010 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - "The Economy of the District of Columbia: Its Changing Structure, Importance to the Region and Opportunities for Future Growth", Circa 2010 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - "International Business In The Greater Washington Region: Scope, Impact, And Competitive Position", November 14, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - "Economic and Fiscal Impact of the Prince William County Proposed 1997 Comprehensive Plan", July 30, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - International Business in the Greater Washington Region Report, April 1998 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Infocomm in the Washington Area Economy, December 1998 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - "The Economic and Fiscal Implications of Hosting the 2012 Olympic Games on the Washington-Baltimore Metropolitan Area", December 2000 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - "The Fiscal Impact of the Proposed CAPCO Program on the District of Columbia Economy", February 2001 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - "The Economic and Fiscal Impacts of the American Pharmaceutical Association's Proposed Headquarters Expansion", August 2001 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Washington D.C. Technological Report, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - "The Economic and Fiscal Impact of Foreign Missions on the National Capital Region", June 2002 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - "Framework for Planning Eisenhower West", September 2002 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - "The Fiscal Impact of the Proposed Breckenridge, New Haven, River Club Commercial, and Heatherstone Commercial Developments", June 2002 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - "The Economic and Fiscal Impact of the Proposed Embassy Suites hotel at 1000 K Street, N.W. Washington, D.C.", December 9, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - "The Economic Impacts of the Proposed Washington Adventist Hospital", August 2011-January 2015 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Conference notes for the Washington Regionalism Initiative Council, circa 2010 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - "The Impact of the 2010 National Marathon on the District of Columbia and Washington Area Economies", January 2011 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - "The Impact of the Proposed Union Market 6th Street Corridor Project on the District of Columbia Economy", May 2011 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - "The New Economy Reality for the Washington Metropolitan Area", February 2013 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - "The Impact of Annual Operating and Capital Outlays by Dominion Virginia Power", January 2013 (Box 27, Folder 9)